<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Weather Radar HR and SLO</string>
    <string name="main_activity_title">Weather Radar</string>
    <string name="img_unavailable">Radar image currently unavailable.</string>
    <string name="widget_slo">Weather Radar SLO</string>
    <string name="widget_hr">Weather Radar HR=</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="help">Help and Tips</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="ads_disabled">Ads disabled</string>
    <string name="refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="animation_rate">Animation Rate</string>
    <string name="freeze_time">Pause before repeating</string>
    <string name="title_show_age_of_every_frame">Show age of every animation frame</string>
    <string name="summary_show_age_of_every_frame">
        On: age text changes with each frame\nOff: shows age of the animation as a whole
    </string>
    <string name="about_text">
Version %1$s
\n© 2018 Belotron d.o.o.\n\nApp icon made by DinosoftLabs from www.flaticon.com
\n\nRadar image SLO © Slovenian Environment Agency
\n\nRadar image HR © Meteorological and Hydrological Service
    </string>
    <string name="help_text">
        Rains almost never appear right above you, the clouds reach you from
        some direction carried by winds. Owing to this you can take a look at
        the weather radar animation and predict whether and when the rains will
        hit you, up to several hours in advance.
        \n
        \nThis app displays the animations published by the Croatian
        Meteorological and Hydrological Service and the Slovenian Environment
        Agency. These are the best sources, “from the horse’s mouth”, for this
        region.
        \n
        \nSome usage tips:
        \n
        \n- Double-tap an image to focus on it. You can pinch-zoom the image. To
        get back, double-tap again or press the Android Back-button.
        \n
        \n- Place the app\'s widget on your home screen to have quick access to
        the current radar image.
        \n
        \n- Tap the widget image to start the app.
        \n
        \nThe app uses OCR to read the image\'s timestamp, translates it to your
        timezone, and shows it above the image. Sometimes the websites stop
        updating their images, in that case you\'ll see the image\'s age growing.
        Once the age reaches one hour, the text turns red to alert you that the
        image is no longer up-to-date.
        \n
        \nThe app is very conservative with internet traffic usage and never has
        to fetch the same image twice, but you always get the latest images thanks
        to the If-Modified-Since HTTP headers. Owing to this, sometimes an image
        refresh takes just fraction of a second, but you can rest assured that we
        contacted the server and it replied that you already have the latest image.
        If we can\'t contact a server, the title above its image will say “Offline”.
    </string>
</resources>
